<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<Product VersionDateTime="2023-05-23 14:55:07" UpdateType="AddOrUpdate"><Identity><ProductCodes><Code Scheme="GTIN">101010101</Code><Code Scheme="IMPACTSCORE:PVID">1010101011684850028</Code></ProductCodes><Subscription Id="48541" Code="ALAR002">Supernoodles plc</Subscription><DiagnosticDescription Code="en-GB">Chicken Flavoured Supernoodles</DiagnosticDescription><DefaultLanguage>en-GB</DefaultLanguage></Identity><Data><Language Code="en-GB" Source="OffPack" GroupingSetId="0" GroupingSetName="No Grouping"><Description>  SUPER NOOD A TASTY CU FLAVOUR READY IN 4 Super No Tasto MINUTES Dried noodles ina seasoning wich peu Per pot (265g) as prepared Energy Ingredients as sold: 1473KJ 18% Noodles (80%) (Wheat Flour: Find 351kcal Lactate, Citric Acid), Salt, Forour E Antioxidant (Tocopherol-Rich Ele Fat 15.0g 21% Agent (Sodium Carbonate) (19%), Ground Turmeric, Yane bene Saturates (Monosodium Glutamate 7.6g 38% Potassium Chloride St, Thatone Onion Powder, Tomato hovor Sugars Chili Powder, Clove Extract Gum 3.9g 4% Allergy Advice: For albo see ingredients in bold Salt May also contain celen, of an adult's Reference Intake* 1.51g 25% molluscs, mustard, sexamen Produced in Hungary: Per 100g (as prepared): Energy 556kJ/133kcal  CURRY FLAVOUR IT'S SUPER SIMPLE ... 2 3 Fil me to POUR IN BOILING WATER LEAVE FOR 2 MINUTES, WAIT 2 MORE MINUTES, TO THE FILL LINE THEN STIR ENJOY! TAKE CARE! CONTENTS WILL BE HOT. CUSTOMER QUALITY GUARANTEE. We want you to enjoy this product.Ifyou have any questions or comments, please contact our Consumer Relations Department 0800 222722 Mon - Fri 9am - 5pm (UK only) quoting the codes printed on the pack Or write to us at UK: FREEPOST PREMIER FOODS CONSUMER RELATIONS. Or ROI: Premier Foods ROI, PO Box No 13008, Dublin 1, Ireland. BATCHELORS trade marks, designs and logos appearing on this pack are owned by the Premier Foods Group. 5 DO NOT USE IF LID IS OPEN OR TORN. 000354 907371 &gt; Splaton Potassium Colour (Carotenes), Store in a cool, dry place. tomate, Flour Treatment esitare, Sugar, Dried Peas NUTRITION INFORMATION panur etancers TYPICAL VALUES PER 100g PER POT (265g) en fati. Powder, Energy AS PREPARED AS PREPARED genel Ground Fennel Seed, protre, Cardamom Oil, Fat 556kJ/133kcal |473KJ/35 l kcal 5.7g 15.0g of which Saturates 2.9g 7.6g W des containing gluten, Carbohydrate of which Sugars 17.4g 46.1g Fibre 1.5g 3.9g 2.7g Protein 1.0g V 275g ℮ 2.5g 6.6g Salt 0.57g 1.51g * Reference Intake of an average adult (8400kj/2000kcal) CUID Recycle This pot contains I portion POT Recycle For Best Before End see base of pot.  SUPER NOODLES IN A TASTY CURRY FLAVOUR SAUCE Fill me to here Super Noodles POUR DEN Tastyny CUSTOMER have any ora 0800 27 Dried noodles in a curry flavour Or write zu seasoning with peas and tomato. OF ROL BATCHEIO Dlg as prepared on this pal Ingredients as sold: DO NOT! 118% Noodles (80%) (Wheat Flour, Palm Oil, Potato Starch, Acidity Regulators (Potassium Lactate, Citric Acid), Salt, Flavour Enhancer (Monosodium Glutamate), Colour (Carotenes) Antioxidant (Tocopherol-Rich Extract), Stabiliser (Potassium Carbonate), Flour Treatment Agent (Sodium Carbonate)), Maltodextrin, Wheat Flour, Maize Starch, Sugar, Dried Peas (1%), Ground Turmeric, Yeast Extract, Dried Tomato (0.5%), Flavour Enhancers (Monosodium Glutamate, Disodium 5'-ribonucleotides), Flavouring, Garlic Powder; Potassium Chloride, Salt, Thickener (Guar Gum), Ground Anise Seed, Ground Fennel Send Onion Powder, Tomato Powder, Acid (Citric Acid), Black Pepper Extract, Cardamom CA ofene Chili Powder, Clove Extract, Ground Cardamom, Ground Coriander, Parsley. see ingredients in bold. May also contain celery, crustaceans, fish, milk, of an adult's Reference Intake molluscs, mustard, sesame and soya. Produced in Hungary. 2 75 g ℮ Per 100g (as prepared): Energy 556kJ/133kcal  CUKR Batchelor's SUPER - Super Tastyry DODAES</Description><Categorisations><Categorisation Scheme="BRANDBANK"><Level Code="00">Ready_Made_Foods</Level><Level Code="00">Snacks</Level><Level Code="00">undefined</Level></Categorisation></Categorisations><ItemTypeGroup Id="0" Name="All Attributes"><Statements Id="2" Name="Lifestyle"><Statement Id="69">No Added Salt</Statement></Statements><Statements Id="2" Name="Lifestyle"><Statement Id="69">Non Alcoholic</Statement></Statements><Statements Id="2" Name="Lifestyle"><Statement Id="69">Suitable for Vegans</Statement></Statements><longtextitems><longtextitem Id="1" Name="Ingredients"><Text>ingredient1</Text></longtextitem></longtextitems><longtextitems><longtextitem Id="1" Name="Ingredients"><Text>ingredient2</Text></longtextitem></longtextitems><longtextitems><longtextitem Id="1" Name="Ingredients"><Text>ingredient3</Text></longtextitem></longtextitems><longtextitems><longtextitem Id="1" Name="Ingredients"><Text>ingredient4</Text></longtextitem></longtextitems><TextualNutrition Id="85" Name="Nutrition"><Headings><Heading>Per 100g</Heading></Headings><Nutrient><Name>Fat</Name><Values><Value>2.0</Value></Values></Nutrient><Nutrient><Name>of which saturates</Name><Values><Value>3.0</Value></Values></Nutrient><Nutrient><Name>of which sugars</Name><Values><Value>1.0</Value></Values></Nutrient><Nutrient><Name>Salt</Name><Values><Value>4.0</Value></Values></Nutrient></TextualNutrition><NumericNutrition Id="86" Name="Calculated Nutrition"><Per100Unit>g</Per100Unit><Per100Heading>per 100</Per100Heading><PerServingHeading>Per 30g Serving</PerServingHeading><NutrientValues Id="1189" Name="Fat (g)"><Per100><Value>2.0</Value></Per100></NutrientValues><NutrientValues Id="1190" Name="of which saturates (g)"><Per100><Value>3.0</Value></Per100></NutrientValues><NutrientValues Id="1186" Name="of which sugars (g)"><Per100><Value>1.0</Value></Per100></NutrientValues><NutrientValues Id="1214" Name="Salt (g)"><Per100><Value>4.0</Value></Per100></NutrientValues></NumericNutrition></ItemTypeGroup></Language></Data></Product>